Five packs of Seven Stars.
-That one we don't have.
-Then give me ten packs.
-Seven packs okay?
-Two packs are enough.
Hey.
Hey, stop!
If you didn't steal anything,
then what's the hurry?
I don't know what your problem is.
If you falsely accuse me, I can--
You look crooked. I've been watching you.
Aunt, I saw what he did.
Can't you see I'm busy? Go watch the door.
What?
He only had 200 on him.
What are you staring at?
You can't even guard a door.
Money sink.
If your mother hadn't died so young,
I'd be free of you.
I'm sick of looking at that sad face.
Hey.
No need to wait till closing
to come back for it.
I took three grand as commission.
Where are you?
Why aren't you guarding the door?
I went to buy food. I thought you wanted
something for your lover.
You got a death wish? Watch that mouth.
Get back here.
Make a sound and you're dead.
THE FIXERS
DOG EAT DOG
Madam Fan's expecting me.
Dead or disappeared.
The client doesn't care.
Just as long as it's taken care of.
Okay.
Madam Fan.
I heard you had one old
and one young competitor.
It's true. We share the same objective.
Maybe there was a problem
on the client's end. I'll handle it.
During it all,
something of mine was taken.
I'd like it back.
This necklace. Who is it from?
I've never seen you without it.
Where did you get it?
It's sort of an ancestral heirloom.
Hmm.
Then you should have it returned.
Go back home first.
For this case,
wait to hear from me before you proceed.
Uh-huh.
Hey, Tai.
Tai, the director generals
made their choice.
X: DID YOU DELETE
ALL THE VIDEOS ON YOUR END?
And now to a tragedy
that shocked the entertainment world.
An explicit video of Sheng…
FIXER GOLD
Oh, shut up.
Sweet and sour pork ribs again.
I thought I told you to call.
Don't just arrive at the office. Get it?
I did, but you didn't answer.
Look, man, I'm a poor dad
just trying to make a living.
Uh, why are we talking to four-eyes?
I don't have to listen to you.
I've got presbyopia.
Wear glasses or your eyes will go bad.
There are some scumbags
I need you to look up.
Can't you wait for me to pick up my kids
and go home first?
This isn't something you do
when you finish your chores.
The chairman wants this case closed
by tomorrow.
Oh, that's tough.
-I want 40%.
-You're joking.
-It's a rip-off.
-Mister, I'm raising a kid.
I… I gotta have eye surgery.
-40%.
-Hey, hey, hey.
So what? You got a kid. I got a kid.
We all gotta make do.
You. It comes out of your cut.
I want you to look into
this Emperor Tai's account.
Sheng messaged him
to see if the videos had been deleted,
which means
he's got Sheng's video selfies.
He could be the one who leaked them.
Oh, okay.
My manager needs me back coding.
Hey, can you clean up?
If I find him, I'll call.
If you clean up, I'll pay the 40%.
Fuck, I don't believe this guy's broke.
He got a drink, and he didn't drink it.
That's poverty, all right.
Psst, hey.
I got a couple of questions.
You have so many. Yeah?
So we've already deleted
Ms. Yen's daughter's videos.
So why are we still investigating?
Sheng's videos went online,
so we have to find the source of the leak.
Okay, all right.
Show this scumbag a good lesson.
Hmm…
We're not gonna get results too quickly
from four-eyes, are we?
Stealth does
the temple's best intelligence reporting.
Hey. You're thinking of
slacking off already?
What, me? No.
It's just that my…
my son just finished his midterms,
and I promised to take him out
for a nice meal.
That's okay.
We'll have a meal another day.
All right, where are we going?
Look, he probably won't get onto it
straight away.
You go ahead.
What?
Are you fucking with me now?
Hey, it won't be that easy
to lose me, all right?
Just keep your phone on.
Respond when there's intel, you hear me?
Fireworks end each year and such.
Thanking you very much.
Yes, indeed.
-Hey.
-What?
What was your second question?
Oh, what goes after "all around
mountains and waters combined"?
Hey, hey.
You're not so divine, idiot.
SWAMP EEL NOODLES
Hey. What's the occasion for the feast?
My son was the top of the class,
so of course we're celebrating.
-That's right.
-Oh, that's great. Well done.
-Thanks.
-It's only midterms.
You make it sound like university.
The gambling joint's been doing so well,
your dad suddenly gave me 300,000.
I wonder where he got that.
I've been lucky lately.
And the gambling joints
had so many customers,
I haven't been able to call.
Oh, is that so?
If business is doing that good,
how about you help me
purchase some seafood?
-Dad, what's wrong?
-What?
-Uh, why is your hand shaking?
-Hmm? Is it?
Uh, it's work-related.
I shake that cup every day,
and now it's become a reflex.
-It'll settle down.
-This is serious.
You might need to schedule a full checkup.
A client of mine, you know, Old Hsiao,
he went to get a checkup,
didn't think anything of it.
They diagnosed sarcopenia.
Use your brain. Hsiao's over 70 years old.
-Don't compare that goat to me.
-Oh, I'm worried about you.
Hey don't leave those.
We gotta eat them all.
-Uh-huh.
-The rest we can take with us.
You don't need to tell us.
We'll eat these as well. Oh yeah.
You're clever, aren't you?
-Hey, you eating?
-Yes.
-You need to stay number one.
-You make it sound like that's easy.
-It's easy for you. You're great.
-No, it's not. I studied for a long time.
You're my son.
Got the powder. Got the pills.
Whoa, what the fuck? Where's number four?
I was raided the other day.
It's the best I can do.
I'm gonna need that. Make it up to me.
No problem.
What's up, bro?
Give it to me. Hand it over.
Hurry.
Crazy, man.
Have you found the phone?
How, man?
Want me to call the cops?
No. Why would I want that?
I'm just wondering if there's anything
that can be traced back to me on it.
Really?
I'm in trouble.
All you care about is yourself.
Calm down, man. Hey, calm down.
Hey, we're thick, man.
We're in this together, yeah?
How many years
we've been working together?
I rely on you to get clients.
Don't worry, man.
Things will die down
and it'll all be over, okay?
The leak? Who the fuck cares, man?
They'll see it and forget it.
That woman died.
The sponsors are getting out.
-That's what this is all about.
-It's okay. It's okay.
That woman's death
wasn't your fault, okay?
You video'd it.
You didn't distribute it, okay?
And that woman?
Hey, she had such a conscience
blurring her face, huh?
Hey.
Still holding?
Give me some more.
You're fucking addicted, bro.
Hey, listen, listen. Hey.
If the cops ask you anything,
remember, I never existed, all right? Hey.
You've been doing this for over ten years,
and every case,
you still handle them personally.
Hmm.
This client,
they went to Yeh Yueh Tong
behind our back.
Something's not right.
When you see the client later, watch them.
If Fixer Lunar knew
that you weren't showing up
and instead were sending me,
I'd imagine she'd feel insulted.
In Cheng He, you're the most senior
and hold the highest rank.
Why would she feel insulted?
Besides, you still call her Fixer Lunar.
Is that honor not enough?
It's become a habit after all this time.
It means nothing, really.
It's the same
as when I accidentally address you
as Fixer Solar.
I don't know the rules you two have,
so that's why I hired you both.
It's all right.
I know that you love your daughter.
There is an order to things at all times.
Can I ask, Prosecutor,
which side did you hire to begin with?
Ching He.
However,
the first to accept
may not be the best for the job,
be it a case or a new position.
I think you'd agree with that.
The videos those lowlifes
filmed have already gone viral.
I'm worried my daughter's could be next.
You said that you'd deal with it
even if it meant killing someone.
I don't care that you're competing.
You received the money, so get it done.
If you have to work together
or whatever, do it.
I just want my daughter to be safe.
Please.
Although Yeh Yueh Tong and Ching He
have never worked together before,
if it helps finish the job,
I'm for it this time.
The Emperor Tai account belongs
to someone called Cho Wen-tai.
He owns a nightclub called Ash.
I restored a conversation
between him and Sheng.
He's been selling drugs to Sheng
for a long time,
as well as a lot of other celebrities,
but that isn't even the craziest part.
Sheng brings women to the nightclub,
and Cho Wen-tai drugs them.
But it's just the tip of the iceberg.
There's definitely more people involved.
We should clarify something.
Before this discussion continues,
Ching He Temple just found out
that three years ago, your daughter
was in a vegetative state in hospital.
And so it would be impossible
for her to film a video with Sheng.
Ms. Yen.
What exactly is your motive
for this commission?
You here for Cho Wen-tai?
Give it to me now.
You here for this case
or you just want that?
Both.
Next time, ring ahead.
I'd have brought it if you had.
So how are you going to get close
to Cho Wen-tai?
Use the Sheng way again?
Mission cancelled.
SIR HONG: MISSION CANCELED
The commission is cancelled.
-Stand down.
-Why?
The client was lying.
Her real target is Cho Wen-tai.
Cho Wen-tai traffics drugs
and works with Sheng
to drug and rape girls.
But we don't have
enough proof to prosecute.
Tai.
And we're getting pressure
from higher up to stop investigating.
That girl with her hair in buns
dancing like a crazy person.
-See her?
-Yeah.
-Take her to the VIP room.
-Okay.
Hey, not the two ugly ones with her.
So your goal was to make us
investigate Cho Wen-tai,
not make the videos disappear.
Am I right?
If you'd seen this happen to your child,
you wouldn't let these creatures
get away with it.
Using both Yeh Yueh Tong
and Ching He as your police?
Ooh! That's fun.
Ching He is immediately terminating
your commission.
The payment will be fully refunded.
Don't you care about the women
Cho Wen-tai has already harmed?
Fixers are not legal tools
to help with your prosecutions.
Despite Cho Wen-tai's appalling actions,
they're not at all important to us.
Since Ching He's pulling out,
I am as well.
I don't take their hand-me-downs.
The female model's video.
It was you who posted that online.
Yes.
Of course I did that.
Otherwise, those monsters
would never have been exposed.
No one would ever know,
and no one would care.
Do you think
that sacrifice was worth it now?
If sacrificing one person
can prevent more people from being harmed,
in all honesty,
it's worth it.
That's it? We let him free?
Fixer Gold,
the commission has been canceled.
Any actions from here on
you perform alone.
-Hello?
-Finished dinner?
Obviously. Have you checked the time?
Come to the address I sent you
and write down
every single word I say next.
-Dad, what are you doing?
-Uh?
Hey, it's the middle of the night.
Why aren't you in bed?
-Doing practice problems.
-Didn't you just finish exams?
That was midterms.
Now I've got the unified.
Look, buddy,
you do this for long,
you'll burn out in six months.
You're burnt out.
Mom told you to go to the doctor,
but you keep stalling.
The watch announces the coming of the sun.
Your dad now has to shit a tonne.
Oh, you've been bound up for so long,
it's finally coming out, is it?
Sorry, uh, can you repeat that again?
Go get yourself a checkup.
You're being funny, are you?
Sheng, once a darling of the music scene
and highly sought after by sponsors,
has now become a hot potato for brands.
Today, a popular mobile phone company
terminated all partnerships with Sheng,
pulling all ads
from the street and online.
UNKNOWN: IF YOU WANT TO KNOW WHO POSTED
YOUR VIDEOS, GO TO THE BACK OF ASH ALONE.
It's rumored that three further brands
have called off talks with Sheng
due to the scandal. Having fallen
from the peak of superstardom,
Sheng is now…
BREAD AND CAKES
Oh, damn it.
Heavier than he looks.
Hey. Wait there.
You can't enter through here.
What's this?
I get five million
when you're dead.
Hey! Who wants to kill me?
What the fuck?
Who the fuck are you?
Ah!
Ah, fuck!
I get five million if I kill you.
Who the fuck wants to kill me?
I'm the kind of person
who'll talk for a price.
You wanna know something,
you need to pay, okay?
I'll give you 800.
Who wants to take me out?
Cho Wen-tai.
It's Sheng.
He thinks you know too much.
-He thinks you leaked his sex videos.
-He wants to silence you.
Sex videos? You gotta be crazy.
He did that?
You're under a lot of scrutiny.
Cops questioned you.
You could have spilled the lot.
Son of a bitch. He's burning bridges now!
Who's out there?
-Help!
-Save your breath.
There's no one there.
Sorry. I'm getting paid to do it.
Wait!
I'll give you double
if you kill him.
You want him dead? How and how much?
I'll give you ten million.
But how you do it, I couldn't care.
Sheng wants to kill me?
I don't believe it.
Sheng doesn't have the balls.
Tell me! Who wants to kill me?
We killers like to do this
in case the client reneges.
I'll give you ten million.
But how you do it, I couldn't care.
Oh shit.
Yeah?
Huh.
He's with me now.
Fuck, I'm doing it.
Fuck you, Cho Wen-tai.
Shh.
What? Fuck, you're kidding me, aren't you?
You want to haggle over it now?
Fuck. Forget it. Fuck!
I'm not killing you now.
Asshole went back on his word.
Motherfucker!
He wants to haggle. Costs are high, huh?
-Where is he?
-At the nightclub office.
Wait. How much did you just offer?
I won't back out.
Good. Yeah, good.
Hey, is this yours?
Yes. Why?
Here, have some.
It'll make you feel a little better, yeah?
Oh… Uh, here.
Yeah?
Mm-hmm.
Okay.
-He wants to see you.
-Fuck you.
-You motherfucker!
-You leak my videos, then wanna kill me!
-Put a price on my head?
-Fuck!
Trying to silence me?
I picked up chicks for you.
And you put a hit on me.
Fuck you.
You only sleep with drugged-out zombies.
You need me to score.
They're going for it.
Hi there. There's been a crime. Mm-hmm.
-You put a fucking hit on me?
-There's fighting at the Ash disco.
Hey.
What goes on up in your head?
-How did you come up with this?
-Fuck.
It's Fixer Shadow's favorite.
Always works a treat.
Uh? Well, in the old days,
things were so much easier.
It's better to get on
a brother's wrong side than a fixer's.
How's Shadow doing?
You fired the shot. What do you think?
Oh, hey, I'm really sorry.
I'll go and apologize.
I will.
The commission was cut short.
Are you saying you had nothing to do
with them turning on each other?
I just wanted to make sure
that our plan would go smoothly.
Cho Wen-tai is despicable.
But I'm warning you
not to break the rules again.
And your code name from now on
is Fixer Fortune, as in good fortune.
Fortune? Well, that's fortunate.
-Hey, did you hear that? Fixer Fortune.
-Butthole.
Did I pass probation?
Go home and rest first.
When there is a new commission,
you'll hear from us.
Young man, you couldn't stand
what Cho Wen-tai did, could you?
That's none of your business.
Again, huh?
Hard to get along with, aren't you?
So very handsome but moody.
Such a waste, seriously.
Hot on the heels of a sex video scandal,
Sheng is in trouble again.
Video footage of him tussling
with nightclub tycoon Cho Wen-tai
went viral today.
During the two-minute altercation,
explosive terms such as drugged,
unconscious, and drug trafficking…
Hey, Stealth.
I'm going to send you a photo.
It's a woman I need checking.
Don't pull out the weapons.
L… let's chill.
Talking or not?
Gerald wanted a hand.
But he got a call and left super quick.
That's the last I heard of him.
Who was it?
Don't tell anyone I told you.
It was the leader of San He,
Lin Wan-li.
Last time, when our ship was
bringing in cargo and got searched,
did you go and handle it?
Sorry, boss, I'm not sure.
Pin's in charge of that.
Is that right?
SAN HE BATHHOUSE
You've seen this woman?
No, I haven't.
This coin's only found here.
Are you positive?
So many people come through.
How should I know?
BEN
Who are you to her?
A friend.
What time are you meeting her?
You're a man.
You say you're after this girl.
What is it you really want?
-Keep watch.
-Okay.
Do I have to keep repeating myself?
I said I would handle that consignment.
Do you understand?
Who, then? Hsiu?
Who said you should do that?
Fuck all this fucking around.
Hey, Pin.
You're very capable.
But sometimes being capable isn't enough.
Hsiu's experience will make things
go a lot smoother.
A man who can't check his anger
can't keep checks on anyone.
San He will one day
be run by the two of you.
Harmony is the key.
Shall we see you off… brother?
Forget it.
-Do it over there, damn it.
-That's enough.
-Look over there.
-What? Want this?
-Stupid.
-Take it. Here you go.
That burns! Oh!
How old are you guys?
-What?
-Who?
-Shit, it's Boss Wan.
-What? Shit.
-I'm 20, Boss Wan.
-Boss Wan, hi, I'm 18.
At your age,
don't forget.
The guys you work with,
these are your true brothers.
Try not to argue, fall out.
-Okay?
-Okay.
Boss Wan, we'll see you off.
What's with seeing me off, huh?
What's going on?
Am I gonna die? Is that it?
-That's why you're so eager to see me off?
-No, Boss Wan. We're sorry.
Sorry, Boss Wan.
He should be a fixer too.
Is he your partner?
Release him.
Tell me why,
Mina Shen.
Mina Shen facts.
She was orphaned when she was very young.
Raised by her aunt
who ran a gambling den.
Can't you see I'm busy?
Outstanding student
who went on to study chemical engineering.
My goodness. I can't believe
you were a top student.
How dare you. You think you can--
-Why are you treading on our toes?
-Who's harassing who now?
Yeh Yueh Tong's interfering,
so Ching He has to pay a visit.
Is that it?
Have you come to warn me?
Or to see me?
I came to warn you.
And to see you. That fine?
I told him I was your friend.
And then I was treated as a foe.
I thought I'd just hand back this.
Hand it over now.
Stay out of my way, will you?
There's money for medical expenses.
Don't get up.
Mm, mm.
Fuck!
Ching He's discovered your identity.
-If Yeh Yueh Tong finds out…
-That's fine.
It's between me and him.
I think
that you should stop investigating.
If Gerald doesn't ever wanna get found,
no amount of searching will help.
I feel that
I will find him.
I gotta go now.
Already? What's the rush?
Use the ointment.
Young people, for fuck's sake.
What a disaster.
If I wasn't crippled in one leg,
that guy would have been on the floor.
Although, I got some US dollars.
Make a sound and you're dead.
Give me the phone.
I don't wanna kill you.
But that guy, he will.
When I bring the knife down,
you walk away. You saw nothing.
If you talk,
I'll use this phone to track you.
Your family as well.
Thank you.
This time, where do you want the body?
Put it in that woman's room.
When she wakes and sees the body,
she'll spill everything.
Really? Look, I know we're friends,
but this time I'm charging a call-out fee.
My car's turning into
your personal hearse.
Yeh Yueh Tong paying you enough?
Want me to talk to Madam Fan for you?
You get fucked.
-You want me to die, do you?
-Get out of here.
Give me back my phone.
Lower your gun. I'll handle it.
If I go back without it…
…I'll be beaten to death.
How much did you see?
You took it just now,
my phone, and forgot to give it back.
Can I have it?
I didn't see anything.
If I return it,
do you promise
you won't remember anything?
At the corner of the alley,
there was this token and some blood too.
Take care of it.
Hold it high, so I can get a good look.
How old are you?
16.
Mm.
What were you doing at 16?
16?
-Remembering 36 is a stretch.
-I want to learn.
Teach me to fire a gun.
Do you know what we do?
You're going to threaten someone…
with a body.
You're telling me you did see something?
If I'm an accessory,
does it matter what I saw?
Get me?
I have to say, this girl's a natural.
Clean up what you saw in the alley.
You talking or not?
Gerald wanted a hand.
But he got a call and left super quick.
Who was it?
The leader of Sun He, Lin Wan-li.
Hello!
Hello, my beautiful wife.
I just bought food.
I'm heading back.
Oh, would you like something?
Okay.
Hey, what the…